const maths = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is the equation for sloping lines?',
    selection: ['y = mx + c', 'm = y + cx', 'cx = m + y', 'y = cx + m'],
    answer: 'y = mx + c',
    description: 'The equation of a straight line on a graph is made up of a y term, an x term, and a number and are written in the form of y = mx + c. The slope of the line is known as the gradient and is represented by m in the equation. The point at which the line crosses the y-axis is the c in the equation.',
    level: 1,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Which way does a positive gradient slope?',
    selection: ['Left', 'Right', 'Up', 'Down'],
    answer: 'Right',
    description: 'Direction is important when it comes to determining slope. It’s important to pay attention to whether you are moving up, down, left, or right; that is, if you are moving in a positive or negative direction. If you go up to get to your second point, the rise is positive. If you go down to get to your second point, the rise is negative. If you go right to get to your second point, the run is positive. If you go left to get to your second point, the run is negative.',
    level: 1,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is the equation for vertical lines?',
    selection: ['k = x', 'c = x', 'x = k', 'x = c'],
    answer: 'x = k',
    description: 'The equation of a vertical line always takes the form x=k. Where k is any number and k is also the x-intercept.',
    level: 1,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'How is theoretical probability calculated?',
    selection: ['P = num of favourable outcomes/num of possible outcomes', 'It doesnt need to be calculated', 'P = num of possible outcomes/num of favourable outcomes', 'P = num of favourable outcomes/num of trials'],
    answer: 'P = num of favourable outcomes/num of possible outcomes',
    description: 'Theoretical Probability can be calculated because each outcome has the same chance of occuring. Therefore P = number of favourable outcomes/number of possible outcomes.',
    level: 1,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What should the probability on each group of branches on a probability tree equal?',
    selection: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
    answer: 'One',
    description: 'Sometimes you don’t know whether to multiply or add probabilities. A probability tree makes it easier to figure out when to add and when to multiply. By multiplying along the branches and adding probabilities down the columns the result should always be 1.',
    level: 1,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is the measure of statistical spread?',
    selection: ['Median.', 'Range.', 'Interquartile Range.', 'Mode.'],
    answer: 'Interquartile Range.',
    description: 'The Interquartile range is the measure of the statistical spread, being equal to the difference between the upper and lower quartiles.',
    level: 2,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is the Median?',
    selection: ['The midpoint of the data.', 'The lowest point of the data.', 'The highest point of the data.', 'The difference between the lowest and highest points of data.'],
    answer: 'The midpoint of the data.',
    description: 'The median is the value lying at the midpoint of a distribution of observed values or quantities, such that half of the values fall above it and half of the values fall below it.',
    level: 2,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is the term that is used describe a distribution that has two distinct peaks?',
    selection: ['Symmetrical Distribution', 'Bimodal Distribution', 'Confidence Interval', 'Asymmetrical Distribution'],
    answer: 'Bimodal Distribution',
    description: 'Bimodal Distribution is when there is a distribution that has two distinct peaks.',
    level: 2,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Define the term shift?',
    selection: ['Vertical Position of a graph.', 'Horizontal Position of a graph.', 'Difference between two values.', 'Frequency is much greater than its neighbouring values.'],
    answer: 'Horizontal Position of a graph.',
    description: 'The term shift is defined as horizontal position of a graph along a scale.',
    level: 2,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What is the term used for an error created by the variability of samples?',
    selection: ['Non-Sampling Error', 'Sampling Error', 'Random Sample Error', 'Overlap Error'],
    answer: 'Sampling Error',
    description: 'A Sampling Error is an error created by the variability of samples',
    level: 2,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is the equation for sloping lines?',
    selection: ['y = mx + c', 'm = y + cx', 'cx = m + y', 'y = cx + m'],
    answer: 'y = mx + c',
    description: 'The equation of a straight line on a graph is made up of a y term, an x term, and a number and are written in the form of y = mx + c. The slope of the line is known as the gradient and is represented by m in the equation. The point at which the line crosses the y-axis is the c in the equation.',
    level: 3,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is the measure of statistical spread?',
    selection: ['Median.', 'Range.', 'Interquartile Range.', 'Mode.'],
    answer: 'Interquartile Range.',
    description: 'The Interquartile range is the measure of the statistical spread, being equal to the difference between the upper and lower quartiles.',
    level: 3,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is the equation for vertical lines?',
    selection: ['k = x', 'c = x', 'x = k', 'x = c'],
    answer: 'x = k',
    description: 'The equation of a vertical line always takes the form x=k. Where k is any number and k is also the x-intercept.',
    level: 3,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is the Median?',
    selection: ['The midpoint of the data.', 'The lowest point of the data.', 'The highest point of the data.', 'The difference between the lowest and highest points of data.'],
    answer: 'The midpoint of the data.',
    description: 'The median is the value lying at the midpoint of a distribution of observed values or quantities, such that half of the values fall above it and half of the values fall below it.',
    level: 3,
    subject: 2
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What should the probability on each group of branches on a probability tree equal?',
    selection: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
    answer: 'One',
    description: 'Sometimes you don’t know whether to multiply or add probabilities. A probability tree makes it easier to figure out when to add and when to multiply. By multiplying along the branches and adding probabilities down the columns the result should always be 1.',
    level: 3,
    subject: 2
  }
]

export default maths
